Hello everyone, today we are going to talk about the little techniques to add fonts in colou.
First, import a .dxf file.
In the pop-up window, select the option to convert to font.
This can help you convert the font information in the .dxf file to the font in colou.
After opening, you can see the font information displayed in the window.
If there is no normal display font in your window,
you can find the display font in the 2D window display menu.
Open the display settings and you can see the normal display font.
Then let's check the font information of the sleeve version on the right.
For the fonts that are not correctly identified,
we can add and correct them in colou.
First, let's add the saved font of the sleeve.
You can find the font tool in the 2D tool bar.
Then, click once to add the font.
You can add the font on the two outside pages.
In the property editor,
you can modify the font type,
width and seam type.
Then let's first deal with the sleeve page,
the cross point connection method at the top.
Select this section of the font,
we can find it in the property editor.
In the property editor,
set the cross point as the second type.
Let's see the connection effect of the six types of fonts.
You can adjust it according to the actual craftsmanship.
Next, let's create an uneven width of the seam.
First, select this page line.
In the property editor,
change the seam type to point.
Then we can set the two ends of a line
for different seam widths.
The default is the line type.
The whole seam is the effect of uniform width.
The translation in the software will be updated later.
We can follow the arrow direction in the 2D window.
The effect is the same as in the 2D window.
Change the width of the end to 10 mm.
On the other side,
we can change the width of the seam to the correct 10 mm.
Similarly, we can edit the opening width of the seam.
So we can modify the seam.